Guide to the Bruce Voeller papers, 1956-1990
Voeller, Bruce papers, 1956-1990
- Series I. Subject Files and Correspondence
  - AIDS, See also audiocassette: Plenary-AIDS: Update and Prevention, Mckusick, Voeller, Wyatt
    - Therapy
      - Chlamydia (Box 17, Folder 45)
      - CMV (Box 17, Folder 46)
      - CO Trimoxazole (Box 17, Folder 47)
      - Combination (Box 17, Folder 48)
      - Compound "Q" (Box 17, Folder 49)
      - Cyclosporin (Box 17, Folder 50)
      - Cryptococcus/Cryptosporidium (Box 17, Folder 51)
      - Dapsone (Box 17, Folder 52)
      - DDC (Box 17, Folder 53)
      - DDG (Box 17, Folder 54)
      - DDI (Box 17, Folder 55)
      - D4T (Box 17, Folder 56)
      - Dermatitis (Box 17, Folder 57)
      - Dextran Sulphate (Box 17, Folder 58)
      - Diarrhea (Box 17, Folder 59)
      - EBV (Epstein-Barr Virus) (Box 17, Folder 60)
      - Electricity (Box 17, Folder 61)
      - Erythropoietin (Box 17, Folder 62)
      - Fluconazol (Box 17, Folder 63)
      - Foscarnet (Box 17, Folder 64)
      - Fungal (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Ganciclovir (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Glutathione (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Gonorrhea (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Hepatitis (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Hepatitis A (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Hepatitis C (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Herpes (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - HIV (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Inosine Pranobex (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Interferon (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Interleukin (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Isoprinosine (Box 18, Folder 13)
      - Kaposis Sarcoma (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Leukoplakia (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Microsporidosis (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 17-20)
      - Moluscum (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Mycobacterium/Mycoplasma (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - N-Acetylcysteive (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Nutrition (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Papilloma Virus (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Pentamidine (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Peptide T (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Pneumocystis (Box 18, Folder 28-29)
      - Retinitis (Box 18, Folder 30)
      - Retinoic Acid (Box 18, Folder 31)
      - Reviews (Box 18, Folder 32)
      - Ribavirin (Box 18, Folder 33-35)
      - Rifabutin (Box 18, Folder 36)
      - Scabies (Box 18, Folder 37)
      - Sinuses (Box 18, Folder 38)
      - Staphylococcus (Box 18, Folder 39)
      - Steroids (Box 18, Folder 40)
      - Suramin (Box 18, Folder 41)
      - Syphilis (Box 18, Folder 42)
      - TB (Box 18, Folder 43)
      - Toxoplasmosis (Box 18, Folder 44)
      - UV (Box 18, Folder 45)
      - Vitamin C (Box 18, Folder 46)
      - Warts (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Transmission (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Travel (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Tumors (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - University of California - Funding Requests, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Urine (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Vaccine (Box 18, Folder 53-54)
    - Vaccine-Hepatitis (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Vaginal Secretions (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Vertical Transmission (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Violence (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Viral Entry (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Viremia (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Virus (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Voeller (Box 18, Folder 62)
      - Government Meetings (Box 18, Folder 63)
      - Meetings (Box 18, Folder 64)
      - Meetings (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Talks (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
    - Volunteers/Recruiting (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Wasting (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - W.H.O. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Women (Box 19, Folder 7-9)
    - Workplace (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - World AIDS (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Venereal Disease
    - V.D. (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
    - V.D. World Congress: San Juan, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Commission on Professional and Hospital Activities (CPHA) (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - CPHA (Box 19, Folder 16-17)
    - Herpes - Virucides (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Herpes (Box 19, Folder 19-20)
    - International Fertility Research Program (IFRP) (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - North Carolina Conference, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - IFRP (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - IFRP Contract (Box 19, Folder 24-25)
      - David Edelman (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Jack Ganley (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Liao, Winston (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Laufe, Dr. Leonard (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Curriculum Vitae (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Sex Change (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Buc, Nancy (Box 19, Folder 32-33)
    - Buc, Nancy (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Anal Sex
    - Index/Bibliography (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - To File (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - HIV - Rectal Mode of Transmission (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - A (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - B (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Bolling, David R., M.D. (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - C (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - D (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
    - E, F (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - G (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - H, I (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - J - L (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - M (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - N - Q (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - R (Box 20, Folder 22-23)
    - S - T (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Rectal STDs (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Legal Size (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Rectal STDs (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - U - V (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Voeller (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - W (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - X - Z (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Semen
    - Semen (Box 21, Folder 6-8)
    - 029 Proposal and Grant (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Subjects (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - 029 Expenses (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - 030 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Pilot 031 - Friction Machine - Proposal and Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - HIV/CMV (Box 21, Folder 14-15)
    - Physical/Chemical (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Vagina, etc. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Vaginal (Box 21, Folder 18-19)
    - Vaginal-Intracondom Coital Pressure Study-132 (Box 21, Folder 20-21)
  - AIDS Conferences
    - Groves, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Paris, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - International AIDS Conference 1: Atlanta, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - International Conference on AIDS IV, V, VII, 1988, 1989, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Stockholm, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 25-26)
    - Montreal, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 26-27)
    - San Francisco, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Montreal, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Florence, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Amsterdam, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Berlin, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - International Society for Advancement of Humanistic Studies in Gynecology (ISAHSG), 1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - NICHD OBGYN, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - NICHD OBGYN, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - International Academy of Sex Research (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research HIV Leakage (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - AIDS Files: Miscellaneous Anderson/Scofield (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - AIDS Files: Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Condoms
    - Breakage (Box 22, Folder 12-14)
    - Clinical Data #1 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Clinical Data #2 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
    - Virus (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - HIV/Viral Leakage (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Glove Leakage (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Nonoxynol-9 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Reviews (Box 22, Folder 22-23)
    - Danielson, Ross (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Reviews: Family Health International (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Reviews: Journal of AIDS (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Koop (C. Everett Koop, U.S. Surgeon General) (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - pH (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Questionnaires (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - AIDS Miscellaneous
    - AIDS Miscellaneous (Box 22, Folder 30-31)
    - "AIDS" (The Name) (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - NGTF (National Gay Task Force) White House Conference, 3/26/1977, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Brochures (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Condoms (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Semen: Latex (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Spermicides - General
    - Composition and Brands (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Spermicidal Substances (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Spermicide (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - "SGCA" (Spermicidal-Germicidal Compound A) (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
    - Singh (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
    - Ortho FDA and Safety (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
    - Ortho FDA Report (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Pasquale (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Postie (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Rendon (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Pelvic Inflammatory Disorder (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - In Vivo (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Clinical and VD (Box 23, Folder 18-19)
    - Spermicides/VD: In Vitro (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Spermicides/VD (Box 23, Folder 21-22)
  - Spermicides - Subject Files
    - Amoebae and Giardia (Box 23, Folder 23-25)
    - Amoebae and Giardia Slides (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Arnold, R.C. (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Asculai, S.S. (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Betadine (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Bolch, O.H. (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Boston Women's Group (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Chlamydia (Box 23, Folder 32-33)
    - Spermicides (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Kinsey Files
    - Addresses (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Conference-Kinsey (Box 30, Folder 2-3)
    - Miscellaneous articles (Box 30, Folder 4-5)
    - Conference correspondence (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Manuscripts/check list for AIDS and Sex volume (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Finished manuscripts of AIDS and Sex volume (Box 30, Folder 8-10)
    - Bibliographies (Box 30, Folder 11-17)
    - Kinsey library Hu-Z (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Kinsey Institute: Annual Report, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Kinsey Institute: Annual Report, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Finished manuscripts of AIDS and Sex volume (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Kinsey Conference, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Kinsey Conference, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Kinsey Conference, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Reinisch (Box 31, Folder 5-6)
    - Reinisch review (Box 31, Folder 7-10)
    - Reinische-Mariposa board (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Stephanie Sanders (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Sex surveys (Box 31, Folder 13-14)
    - Conference Photo with names (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Reinisch Review (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - AIDS Research and Public Policy Reports
    - Technical Proposal: Spermicides and Sexually Transmitted Diseases, 1983 (Box 31, 42-49, Folder 15)
    - Directory of AIDS/HIV Clinical Trials Open in New York and New Jersey, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Coefficient of Friction (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - AIDS Public Policy Materials Federal and California (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - AIDS in California: A Prescription for Meeting the Needs of 1990, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Summary of Results from HTVL-III Antibody Screen Focus Group Research, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - New York City AIDS Case Projections, 1989-1993 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - AIDS: A Resource Guide for New York (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - AIDS Research and Human Retroviruses, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Preliminary Report of the Task Force on Sexual Preference to the Oregon State Legislature, 1977 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Background material for N.G.T.F. presentation before the Commission October 11, 2:30 P.M., Washington D.C., 1977 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Trimensa Spermicides, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - AIDS Barrier Contraception Investigation
    - ABBY (Dear), 1993 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - AIDS/Barrier Contraception, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - AIDS/ Barrier Contraception Investigation, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - AIDS/ Barrier Contraception Protocol IV Budgets and Appendices, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
    - AIDS/ Barrier Contraception Publicity, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - AIDS / Barrier Contraception Results, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 7-9)
    - AIDS / Barrier Contraception Workshop #1, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Acredition, N.D. (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Advertising for Condoms, 1986-1988 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Advertising for Volunteers, 1982 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Advisory Board (AIDS/ Barrier Contraception and NAT. Hx), 1986 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Aging, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - AIDS (N-9), 1992 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Air Burst, 1988-1990 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Akron, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Anderson and Voeller "AIDS and Contraception", 1993 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Anderson and Voeller Condoms, 1984-1990 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Anderson and Voeller Infection Site, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Anderson and Voeller IUDs Intro, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Anderson and Voeller IUDs Intro, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Anderson/Voeller MSS, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Anderson/Voeller MSS, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Anderson and Voeller-- MISC. Future Resources, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - I. Anderson and Voeller Spermacide, 1990-1992 (Box 42, Folder 27-29)
    - Anderson and Voeller- Sponge Cap Diaphragm, 1984-1991 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Ansell Medical, 1981-1991 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - APEX Medical Technologies, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Archives of Sexual Behavior (AIDS/HT. Anal Intercourse), 1988-1990 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Archives of Sexual Behavior AIDS/Heterosexual Anal Intercourse, 1990-1991 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Articles Re: Condoms, 1988-1992 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - ASTM (American Society for Testing and Materials), 1990-1993 (Box 43, Folder 2-8)
    - ASTM Standards, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Aukland Medical Plastics, 1991-1992 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Bachardy, Don, 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Bachardy (Mariposa) Tour, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Bachardy- MP Catalogue, 1980-1981 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Baxter- Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Baxter MMS STD-2, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 15-17)
    - Baxter- Misc., 1988-1992 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Baxter STI-1, 1992 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Baxter WI 1 London- Report to W1, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Baxter WI 1 London- Report to W1, 1991 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Bermedica, 1990 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Bernstein, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - BOLAN, Dr. Robert, 1982-1984 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Bratt, Erwin, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Brands- Condoms, 1986 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Brochures, N.D. (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Brochures/Promotion/Press, 1986-1993 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - California Food and Drug, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Carter- Wallace, N.D. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Center for Disease Control (Don Hicks), 1985-1986 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - CDC Don Hicks, 1986-1987 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Certification, N.D. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Chartex, 1977-1992 (Box 44, Folder 6-8)
    - Chemistry, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Circle Rubber Corp., 1987-1993 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Clinical Phase II, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Coital Data, 1952-1988 (Box 44, Folder 12-14)
    - College of Health, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Competition, 1982-1984 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Condom Stocks, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Condom Study Comparisons Book 1 (Pleaser/Embrace/Gold Circle/Gold Circle Coin), 1987 (Box 44, Folder 18-22)
    - Condom Study Comparisons Book 2 (Contracept Plus/Arouse/ Sheilds), 1987 (Box 44, Folder 23-25)
    - Condoms to Test, 1987 (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Connant, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - CONRAD- Contraceptive Research and Development Program- Santa Domingo, 1992-1993 (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Consumer's Union, 1980-1988 (Box 44, Folder 29-30)
    - Contraception (Manuscript), 1989-1990 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 45, Folder 6-7)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1992 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Cranks- Opposition and Threats Re: Segal Sculpture, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Donations, 1972-1986 (Box 45, Folder 10-12)
    - Drugs, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Duke Inference Test, 1982-1983 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Education, 1989-1992 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Education Workshop (Morisky), 1987 (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Efficacy, 1983 (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Experimental, 1987-1988 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Failure, 1985-1992 (Box 45, Folder 19-20)
    - FDA (Food and Drug Administration), 1984-1992 (Box 45, Folder 21-23)
    - FDA Hearing (Wisconsin), January 1992 (Box 45, Folder 24)
    - FDA Hearing, January 1992 (Box 45, Folder 25-26)
    - FDA Response, June 1992 (Box 45, Folder 27)
    - FDA Response (WI), October 1992 (Box 45, Folder 28)
    - FDA Response (WI), January 1993 (Box 45, Folder 29)
    - Female Condom, 1987-1991 (Box 45, Folder 30)
    - File Index (Box 45, Folder 31)
    - Final Report Photos (Box 45, Folder 32)
    - Fluorescein, 1991-1992 (Box 45, Folder 33)
    - Fundraising, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 34)
    - Gollub, Erica, 1991-1993 (Box 45, Folder 35-36)
    - Gonorrhea, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Grant - Final Draft (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Grant - Spermicides, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Grants, 1978-1980 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Grants, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Gynecologist, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Heterosexual Anal Sex - Changing Men, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Hicks, Donald, 1987-1992 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Holes, 1991-1992 (Box 46, Folder 9-10)
    - Human Rights Campaign Fund (HRCF), 1982 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Human Subjects and Confidentiality Certificate, 1986 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Informed Consent Form, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Institute/Pomeroy, W, 1982-1983 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Interoffice Memo, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Jick, Hershell, 1980-1981 (Box 46, Folder 16-17)
    - Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA) - Dye/Viral Transport, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - JAMA: pH - HIV, Voeller - Anderson, 1992 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Journal of National Institute of Health - "Research Reveals Condom Conundrums", 1993 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Kinsey - "Admit", 1986-1990 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Kinsey - Anal Intercourse, 1991 (Box 46, Folder 22-23)
    - Kinsey - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 46, Folder 24-25)
    - Kinsey Preface, 1989-1990 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Los Angeles Regional Family Planning Council (LARF)/ National Institute of Child Health and Human Development (NICHD), 1989 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - LARF/NICHD - Condoms, 1989 (Box 46, Folder 28-29)
    - Liao, Winston, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Lubricants, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Lubricants - London, Australia, 1985-1988 (Box 46, Folder 32-33)
    - Manuscripts - AIDS Research, etc., 1993 (Box 46, Folder 34-35)
    - Manuscripts - Semen pH, Tripp, etc, 1988-1993 (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Marioposa, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Mariposa "Occasional Papers", 1983-1993 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Mariposa Press, 1982-1989 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Marisol, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Mayer Labs, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Media - Condoms, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Memos, Agendas, Minutes, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 7-9)
    - Memos - Condoms, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 10-11)
    - Memos etc. Jan 1-June 30, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 12-13)
    - Memos etc. July 1-December 31, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Mentor Condoms, 1986-1989 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Mercer, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Military - SPEC (5 copies), 1961 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous with Condom Study Comparisons, 1987-1989 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Contraceptive Information, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous (Notes, Phone Numbers, Etc.), 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Nakamura, Dr. Robert, 1987-1990 (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Nakamura - C.V. (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - National Institute of Child Health and Human Development (NICHD), 1988 (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - National Institute of Health (NIH) Paid, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - National Institute of Health Reimbursement - Paid, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - National Sanitary Labs, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Neisseria Auxotypes, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Neisseria Test Suppression, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Nelson/Grant, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Nelson Labs - Final Report, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Nelson Labs (Phi X) - Correspondence, Detection Limit, Refrigeration-Stability, 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Nelson Labs - Sequoia Associates, 1991-1993 (Box 47, Folder 33-35)
    - New York City, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1983-1988 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Nonoxynol-9, 1984-1985 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Nonoxynol-9 Side Effects, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Ozone, UV, NO2 etc., 1989 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Parachini, 1987-1989 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Parrish Condoms, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Phi X Calcium ++ Dulbecos, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Phi X-174 Data, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Phi X-174, Includes Lab Sheet - Raw Data, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Phi X Lab Data - Tween Stability, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Phi X, PU - Intact, With Holes, 1991-1993 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Phi X Protocol (4 copies) (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Program for the Introduction and Adaptation of Contraceptive Technology (PIACT)/PATH, 1980-1993 (Box 48, Folder 14-15)
    - PIACT Project, 1980-1993 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Pornography/Eroticising, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Press, 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Prostitutes, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Protocol 1, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 20-21)
    - Protocol 2, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 22-23)
    - Publications - Book Lists, Advertisements, Miscellaneous, 1980-1988 (Box 48, Folder 24-25)
    - Putnam, Peter, 1979-1985 (Box 48, Folder 26)
    - Questionnaire, 1987 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    - Rankings - Condoms, 1987-1992 (Box 48, Folder 28-29)
    - References - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987 (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Reimbursed, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 31)
    - Reimburse (To Do), 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    - Religion, 1987-1990 (Box 48, Folder 33)
    - Research, 1982-1985 (Box 48, Folder 34)
    - Reviews - Condoms, 1986-1992 (Box 48, Folder 35-37)
    - Rogue, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 38)
    - Roland, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Sales, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Sample AIDS Surveys (MACS and NYBC), 1985 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Schmid Bergen Brunswick, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Schmid Confidentiality Agreement, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Schmid Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Schmid Labs, 1987-1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Schmid - Money, 1990-1992 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Schmid Protocols, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Schmid P.V., 1990 (Box 49, Folder 10-11)
    - Schmid T and E, 1988-1989 (Box 49, Folder 12-13)
    - Segal Sculpture, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 14-21)
    - Segal Sculpture (Mostly), 1980 (Box 49, Folder 22-23)
    - Segal Sculpture Opposition, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Segal Sculpture Petitions and More, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 25-26)
    - Segal Sculpture Press, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 27-28)
    - Segal Sculpture Support, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Sexually Transmitted Diseases (STDs), 1977-1980 (Box 49, Folder 30-31)
    - SFT Labs, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Singh, Dr. B., 1982 (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Size (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Skins, 1988-1992 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Spermicides (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Spermicides I (Research and Data-Oriented), 1986-1987 (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Spermicides II (Articles), 1982-1986 (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - St. James, Margo (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Staab, Robert PhD, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Standards - Condoms, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Statistics, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Surfactants/AIDS, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 43)
- Series II. Early Scientific Research
  - "Some Alabama Fungi"--Drawings and 1901 Calendar (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Fern diagrams (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Fern photos (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Fungi photos (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Algae photos (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Plant and chromosome photos (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Plant and Plant cell photos and charts (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Palliser, Helen, "The North American Chaetomiaceae" (Box 63, Folder 8)